{
    "subject": "resource/Dublin_North_(D\u00e1il_\u00c9ireann_constituency)",
    "predicate": "property/name",
    "object": "resource/Alan_Farrell",
    "human_readable": "The name of the Dublin North D\u00e1il \u00c9ireann constituency is Alan Farrell.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9764915108680725,
            "question": "What is the name of the Dublin North D\u00e1il \u00c9ireann constituency?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9536730051040649,
            "question": "Who represents the Dublin North D\u00e1il \u00c9ireann constituency?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9081206321716309,
            "question": "In which country would you find the Dublin North D\u00e1il \u00c9ireann constituency?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6571211218833923,
            "question": "Is Alan Farrell a politician?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49941322207450867,
            "question": "Are there other constituencies in Ireland besides Dublin North?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4258301258087158,
            "question": "What are the responsibilities of a D\u00e1il \u00c9ireann representative?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3734820485115051,
            "question": "What type of political body is the D\u00e1il \u00c9ireann?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3641078770160675,
            "question": "Can you name other constituencies in Ireland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31554925441741943,
            "question": "How often are elections held for the D\u00e1il \u00c9ireann?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27638566493988037,
            "question": "What does 'D\u00e1il \u00c9ireann' translate to?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of the Dublin North D\u00e1il \u00c9ireann constituency is Alan Farrell.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4700_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How often are elections held for the D\u00e1il \u00c9ireann?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4700_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name other constituencies in Ireland?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4700_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of political body is the D\u00e1il \u00c9ireann?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4700_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4700_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4700_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4700_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4700_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4700_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4700_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4700_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4700_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4700_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4700_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": -1,
            "full_ans": "The text does not list current representatives for the Dublin North D\u00e1il \u00c9ireann constituency. \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "**Repeat**\n{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n       \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": -1,
            "full_ans": "That information isn't available with the provided context."
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text lists various historical election results and current TDs for Dublin North, and Alan Farrell's name is not mentioned.",
            "category": -1
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The Dublin North D\u00e1il \u00c9ireann constituency is not named Alan Farrell.",
            "category": -1
        }
    }
}